hey everybody
헤이 여러분!
it's Ariannita la Gringa and welcome back to my YouTube channel
Ariannita la Gringa입니다. 제 YouTube 채널에 다시 오신 것을 환영합니다.
in today's video I will ask people around Cincinnati Ohio what they do for a living
오늘 영상에서는 오하이오주 신시내티 주변 사람들에게 무슨 일을 하며
and how much they make each year
, 매년 얼마를 버는지 물어보겠습니다.
let's go
갑시다!
hi what's your name my name is Austin
안녕, 이름이 뭐예요? -제 이름은 오스틴이에요.
hi Austin what do you do for a living I work downtown at divisions maintenance group
안녕 오스틴, 무슨 일을 하시나요? - 저는 부서의 유지 관리 그룹에서 시내에 근무하며
and I manage a book of business for various different clients
다양한 고객의 비즈니스 장부를 관리
and I help them with their facility maintenance
하고 시설 유지 관리를 돕습니다.
when Americans ask what do you do for a living they want to find out your job and what you do for work
미국인들이 "어떤 일을 하시나요?"라고 물으면 그들은 당신의 직업과 당신이 일을 위해 무엇을 하는지 알고 싶어합니다.
what's your favorite part about your job probably my favorite part is
당신의 직업에서 가장 좋아하는 부분은 무엇입니까? - 아마도 제가 가장 좋아하는 부분은
just seeing my client's reaction when I solve a problem for them
고객의 문제를 해결할 때 고객의 반응을 보는 것입니다 .
and then what kind of projects do you work on well right now I won't say the name but I
그럼 어떤 프로젝트를 진행하시나요? -글쎄, 지금은 이름을 밝히지 않겠습니다. 하지만 저는
work for a doughnut company and I help them out with making sure their doughnut line's running
도넛 회사에서 일하며 그 회사의 도넛 라인이 제대로 운영되는지 확인하는 일을 돕고 있습니다.
how many hours do you work each week I'm pushing like 70 hours per week right now
매주 몇 시간 일하시나요? - 지금은 일주일에 70시간 정도 일하고 ​​있어요.
slot after hours
근무 외 시간이 많습니다.
sounds like you work a lot and then how much do you earn each year
일을 많이 하는 것 같던데, 연간 얼마를 벌나요?
right now I'm tracking towards 115
지금은 115,000달러를 향해 가고 있습니다.
hi what's your name Mitch Kaiser
안녕, 이름이 뭐예요? -미치 카이저.
hi Mitch what do you do for a living I work for Pro Football Focus
안녕 미치, 무슨 일을 하시나요? -저는 Pro Football Focus에서 일합니다.
I'm a college football analyst for PFF here in Cincinnati
저는 여기 신시내티에 있는 PFF의 대학 축구 분석가입니다.
what's your favorite part about your job getting to watch every college football game
당신의 직업에서 가장 좋아하는 부분은 무엇입니까? - 모든 대학 미식축구 경기를 시청
and then write about it later on I write articles covering college football
하고 나중에 그것에 대해 글을 쓰게 됩니다. 나는 대학 축구를 다루는 기사를 씁니다.
and what's your favorite article you've written I wrote an article last fall about why Michael Penix should have won the Heisman
그리고 당신이 쓴 글 중 가장 좋아하는 글은 무엇인가요? -지난 가을에 Michael Penix가 Heisman을 수상했어야 했던
I was pretty happy about it and then he
이유에 대한 기사를 썼습니다 . 나는 그것에 대해 매우 기뻤고 그는
played really well so that's probably my favorite article
정말 잘 연주했기 때문에 아마도 내가 가장 좋아하는 기사 일 것입니다.
how many hours a week do you work 40 sometimes more in the season
일주일에 몇 시간 일하시나요? -40. 시즌에는 더 많은 경우도 있습니다.
summertimes you get probably less than 40 cuz it's off season and then when fall rolls
여름에는 비수기이기 때문에 아마도 40시간 미만을 얻을 수 있고 가을에는
around probably like 60 hours some weeks
몇 주에 걸쳐 아마도 60시간 정도 걸릴 것입니다.
in the US a standard work week is 40 hours usually 8 hours a day 5 days a week
미국의 표준 근무시간은 주 5일, 보통 하루 8시간, 40시간입니다.
if you work more than 40 hours that's overtime and you get paid extra
40시간 이상 일하면 초과 근무가 되며 추가 수당을 받게 됩니다.
for example if you make $10 an hour overtime is time and a half so for every hour worked over 40 you'd make $15
예를 들어, 시간당 $10를 벌면 초과 근무는 시간 반이므로 40시간 이상 일한 매 시간에 대해 $15를 벌게 됩니다.
how much do you earn each year not enough not not enough I'm going to say that
매년 얼마를 벌나요? -부족한. 부족한. 나는 그렇게 말할 것이다.
what's the minimum you could earn if you just started out
이제 막 시작했다면 최소한 얼마를 벌 수 있나요?
probably like 30k would be the minimum like the lowest I make a little more than that but not great you know
아마도 30k 정도가 최소값일 것입니다(가장 낮은 것과 같습니다). 나는 그보다 조금 더 벌지만, 별로 좋지는 않습니다.
hi what's your name hi my name's Katie
안녕, 이름이 뭐예요? -안녕하세요, 제 이름은 케이티예요.
hi Katie what do you do for a living I am a server
안녕하세요 케이티, 무슨 일을 하시나요? -저는 서버입니다.
and what's your favorite part about your job I meet so many cool people
그리고 당신의 직업에서 가장 좋아하는 부분은 무엇입니까? -멋진 사람들을 너무 많이 만난다.
especially being downtown I feel like it's such a wide variety of people that I get and it's just really
특히 시내에 있으면 정말 다양한 사람들을 만날 수 있고,
cool to meet so many different kinds of people
이렇게 다양한 사람들을 만날 수 있다는 게 정말 멋진
what do you do every day for your job I go around I get tables and I basically just take
것 같아요 . 당신은 일을 위해 매일 무엇을 합니까? - 돌아다니며 테이블을 마련하고, 기본적으로
their food and drink order chat it up with them and have a good time
음식과 음료 주문을 받고, 이야기를 나누고, 즐거운 시간을 보내고,
do anything they need fill up their Waters keep them happy
필요한 모든 것을 하고, 물을 채우고, 행복하게 해줍니다.
and then what's your least favorite part about your job sometimes like it's really overwhelming
그렇다면 당신의 직업에서 가장 마음에 들지 않는 부분은 무엇입니까? -가끔 너무 부담스러울 때가 있어요.
I love to multitask but sometimes it's like I'm not an octopus
나는 멀티태스킹을 좋아하지만 때로는 문어가 아닌 것처럼 느껴질 때도 있습니다.
it's hard to do 20 million things at once but that's not always all the time that's just really busy days
2천만 가지 일을 한 번에 한다는 것은 어려운 일이지만 항상 바쁜 날만 있는 것은 아닙니다.
it can be overwhelming for sure
확실히 압도적일 수 있습니다.
how many hours each week do you work right now I'm doing about 40
매주 몇 시간 일하시나요? -지금은 40시간 정도 하고 있어요.
during the school year I do like 25 30 so a few days a week
학기 중에는 25~30시간을 좋아해서 일주일에 며칠 정도 해요.
okay so you're a student as well yeah
그렇군요, 그럼 당신도 학생이군요? -응.
what do you study um Speech Pathology
당신은 무엇을 공부합니까? -음. 언어 병리학.
I just graduated yeah oh congrats
나 방금 졸업했어, 응. -아 축하해요!
and then how much do you earn each year each year I think if I was working full-time
그러면 일년에 얼마를 벌어요? -매년 풀 타임으로 일했다면
it would be a lot more but I think this year it was like 25,000 22 25,000 um
훨씬 더 많을 거라고 생각하는데, 올해는 $25,000, $22,000-$25,000 정도였던 것 같아요.
and that's with full-time in the summer and then part-time during the school year
년도.
if you work full-time that means you work around 30 to 40 hours a week and
풀타임으로 일한다는 것은 일주일에 약 30~40시간을 일한다는 의미이며
you often get benefits like health insurance and paid time off
건강 보험이나 유급 휴가와 같은 혜택을 받는 경우가 많습니다.
Katie works part-time so she works fewer hours usually 20 hours or less a week
Katie는 파트타임으로 일하기 때문에 일반적으로 일주일에 20시간 이하로 일합니다.
hi what's your name hi my name is Cameron
안녕, 이름이 뭐예요? -안녕하세요, 제 이름은 카메론이에요.
hi Cameron what do you do for a living currently I work here at Starbucks at 580
안녕하세요 카메론, 무슨 일을 하시나요? -현재 저는 이곳 스타벅스 580에서 일하고 있습니다.
and what do you do for your job I'm a barista I make coffees do food here
당신은 직업을 위해 무엇을 합니까? -저는 바리스타입니다. 나는 여기서 커피를 만들고, 음식을 만들고,
bring out customers and make sure everybody's met with what they need
고객을 데려오고, 모두가 필요한 것을 충족하는지 확인합니다.
what's your favorite part about your job in with the customers for sure
당신의 직업에서 가장 좋아하는 부분은 무엇입니까? -확실히 고객과 함께,
getting to know people as they come in and just being able to make those connections with everybody
사람들이 들어올 때마다 알게 되고, 모든 사람들과 그러한 관계를 맺을 수 있습니다.
and then what's the least favorite part about your job I'm going to hit it with a little comedic joke I would say dishes
그렇다면 당신의 직업에서 가장 마음에 들지 않는 부분은 무엇입니까? - 조금 코믹한 농담으로 요리를 할 거예요.
dishes yeah
그릇? -응.
how many hours do you work each week I work about 30 to 35 hours a week
매주 몇 시간 일하시나요? - 일주일에 30~35시간 정도 일해요.
how much do you earn right now I'm currently making 16.75 an hour
너는 돈을 얼마나 버니? 지금 저는 시간당 16.75달러를 벌고 있습니다.
how much do you earn is just a way of asking someone how much money they make
"너는 돈을 얼마나 버니?" 이는 누군가에게 돈을 얼마나 버는지 묻는 방법일 뿐입니다.
also Cameron gets paid by the hour so he earns more if he works more hours
또한 Cameron은 시간당 급여를 받기 때문에 더 많은 시간을 일하면 더 많은 돈을 벌 수 있습니다.
another way to get paid is with a salary where you get paid the same amount every pay period
급여를 받는 또 다른 방법은 근무 시간에 관계없이
no matter how many hours you work
급여 기간마다 동일한 금액을 받는 급여를 이용하는 것입니다
hi what's your name Orlando Smith
. 안녕, 이름이 뭐예요? -올랜도 스미스.
hi Orlando what do you do for a living Cincinnati law enforcement
안녕 올랜도, 무슨 일을 하시나요? -신시내티 법 집행 기관.
and then what's your favorite part about your job favorite part lunchtime
그렇다면 당신의 직업에서 가장 좋아하는 부분은 무엇입니까? -가장 좋아하는 부분... 점심시간.
lunch time is good because we do so much you never know when you're going to get a lunch break
점심시간은 일이 너무 많아서 좋은 것 같아요. 언제 점심시간을 갖게 될지 모르니까요.
exactly so you could be on a run for several hours and you're
정확히. -그래서 몇 시간 동안 달리면서
standing there thinking cheeseburgers going to be great when it's time to
거기 서서 생각하고 있을 수도 있습니다. 식사 시간이 되면 치즈버거가 정말 맛있을 것 같아요.
what's your least favorite part about your job oh man I think seeing so many victims
당신의 직업에서 가장 마음에 들지 않는 부분은 무엇입니까? -아 이런... 피해자가 너무 많은 것 같아요.
I think we see so many victims of crimes is kind of put you in a not the space in your head
제 생각에는 범죄 피해자가 너무 많아 머리 속이 좋지 않은 공간에 놓일 수 있다고 생각합니다.
and then how many hours do you work each week I do 10 hour day we do 10 hour shifts
그러면 일주일에 몇 시간 일하시나요? -저는 하루에 10시간씩 일해요. 우리는 10시간 교대근무를 합니다.
a shift is a set period of time that you work at your job for example if you work dayshift you might work from
교대근무는 직장에서 일하는 정해진 기간입니다. 예를 들어, 주간 근무를 한다면
9:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m. and if you work night shift you might work from 11:00 p.m. to 7:00 a.m.
오전 9시부터 오후 5시까지 일할 수 있고, 야간 근무를 한다면 오후 11시부터 오전 7시까지 일할 수 있습니다.
we work four on four off for 3 weeks and we work five on three off for 3 weeks
우리는 3주 동안 4일 4일 쉬고 일합니다. 3주 동안 5일 3일 쉬면서 일하세요.
if you don't mind me asking how much do you earn every year I make around a low six figures
실례가 되지 않는다면, 매년 얼마를 벌고 계시나요? - 나는 대략 6만 달러 정도를 벌어요.
six figures means someone makes more than $100,000 a year it's a way of saying they make a lot of money
숫자 6개는 연간 10만 달러 이상을 버는 것을 의미합니다. 돈을 많이 벌었다고 말하는 방식이죠.
and then if someone was just starting out how much would they make as a police officer
그렇다면 누군가가 막 경찰을 시작했다면 경찰관으로서 얼마를 벌겠습니까?
I think tops maybe $80,000 with the city of Cincinnati
내 생각엔 신시내티 시에서 80,000달러 정도를 더 내야 할 것 같아요.
well thank you so much Orlando nice to meet you it's a pleasure
정말 고마워요, 올랜도. 만나서 반가워요. -그것은 기쁨.
hi what's your name I'm Jacob
안녕, 이름이 뭐예요? -저는 제이콥이에요.
hi Jacob what do you do for a living I am a bartender and I work private dining events
안녕하세요 제이콥, 무슨 일을 하시나요? -저는 바텐더이며 프라이빗 다이닝 이벤트를 진행하고 있습니다.
what's your favorite part about your job my favorite part about my job
당신의 직업에서 가장 좋아하는 부분은 무엇입니까? - 내 직업에서 내가 가장 좋아하는 부분은
is the flexible scheduling that it comes with
유연한 일정 관리입니다.
how many hours do you work each week anywhere between 25 and 35
매주 몇 시간 일하시나요? -25세에서 35세 사이.
what is the least favorite part about your job late nights and the occasional rude customer
당신의 직업에서 가장 마음에 들지 않는 부분은 무엇입니까? -늦은 밤에도 가끔 무례한 손님이 옵니다.
how much do you earn each year on paper around 65k
매년 얼마를 벌나요? - 종이에 약 65k.
hi what's your name hi my name's Emilio
안녕, 이름이 뭐예요? -안녕하세요, 제 이름은 에밀리오입니다.
what do you do for a living currently I'm just employed at Planet Fitness
직업이 뭐예요? -현재 저는 Planet Fitness에서
as a front desk employee the things that I love about working at Planet Fitness is that it gives me a free membership
프론트 데스크 직원으로 일하고 있습니다. 제가 Planet Fitness에서 일하면서 좋아하는 점은 무료 멤버십을 제공한다는 것입니다.
I've always wanted to be more into like the active lifestyle and things like that
나는 항상 활동적인 라이프스타일 같은 것에 더 관심을 갖고 싶었습니다.
how many hours do you work each week I think the typical work week about 40 hours I think
매주 몇 시간 일하시나요? -평균적으로 일주일에 40시간 정도 근무하는 것 같아요.
how much do you earn each year I actually don't know cuz I just started this job
매년 얼마를 벌나요? - 사실 잘 모르겠어요. 제가 이 일을 시작한 지
about like three months ago three to four months ago so I haven't done the calculations but it is about minimum wage
석 달쯤 됐으니까, 석 달에서 네 달 정도 되어서 계산은 안 해봤는데 최저임금에 관한 거예요.
minimum wage is the lowest amount of money an employer is legally allowed to pay their workers per hour
최저 임금은 고용주가 법적으로 근로자에게 시간당 지급할 수 있는 최저 금액입니다.
how much is the minimum wage right now it's about like 10 something an hour
지금 최저임금은 얼마인가요? - 한 시간에 10달러 정도 해요.
hi what's your name Brandy
안녕, 이름이 뭐예요? -브랜디.
hi Brandy what do you do for a living I'm a venue manager and event planner
안녕하세요 브랜디, 무슨 일을 하시나요? -저는 공연장 관리자이자 행사 기획자입니다.
what's your favorite part about your job there are a lot but getting able to plan people's special day
당신의 직업에서 가장 좋아하는 부분은 무엇입니까? -많은 일이 있지만 사람들의 특별한 날,
their wedding their events birthday parties that's probably my favorite thing
결혼식, 행사, 생일 파티를 계획할 수 있는 것이 아마도 제가 가장 좋아하는 일일 것입니다.
what's your favorite thing to plan I would say weddings
계획하기 가장 좋아하는 일은 무엇입니까? -결혼식이라고 할까요.
and then what's your least favorite part about your job I'm on call all the time so I never have a day off really
그렇다면 당신의 직업에서 가장 마음에 들지 않는 부분은 무엇입니까? -항상 통화 중이어서 쉬는 날이 없어요.
I'm always answering emails phone calls text messages dealing with Brides
나는 항상 이메일, 전화 통화, 문자 메시지에 응답하고 신부를 상대합니다.
a day off is a day when you do not have to work it's a day you can spend doing whatever you want
쉬는 날은 일을 하지 않는 날이다. 원하는 것을 무엇이든 하면서 보낼 수 있는 날입니다.
how much do you make each year it fluctuates cuz I have a base salary
매년 얼마를 버나요? -기본급
and commission but I live comfortably
과 커미션이 있어서 변동이 심하지만, 편하게 살고 있어요.
if someone was just starting out with event planning how much would they normally
누군가 이벤트 계획을 막 시작했다면 보통 얼마를 벌까요?
make probably 50,000 a year
아마 1년에 50,000달러 정도 할 겁니다.
hi what's your name I'm Ava
안녕, 이름이 뭐예요? -저는 아바예요.
hi Ava what do you do for a living so I just am about to move to Guatemala in June
안녕하세요 Ava, 무슨 일을 하시나요? -그래서 저는 6월에 과테말라로 이주할 예정
and I'm going to be working for a medical clinic through University of Cincinnati
이고, 신시내티 대학을 통해 의료기관에서 일할 예정입니다.
what will be your favorite part about the job I'm really excited to get to work with underprivileged communities in like a medical setting
이 직업에서 가장 좋아하는 부분은 무엇입니까? -의료 분야와 같은 소외 계층 커뮤니티와 함께 ​​일하게 되어 정말 기쁘고
and I hope to go to medical school
의과대학에 진학하고 싶습니다.
that's amazing and do you speak Spanish yes I do
그 놀라운! 그리고 당신은 스페인어를 할 수 있나요? -네 저도 그렇습니다.
and then how many hours will you work each week in Guatemala
그러면 과테말라에서는 매주 몇 시간 일할 건가요?
it depends so when the doctors and med students are going down there
따라서 의사와 의대생이 그곳으로 내려갈 때
it'll be like more of a full-time job working in the clinic
병원에서 정규직으로 일하는 것과 같을 것입니다.
how much will you earn each week it's pretty much a volunteer job
매주 얼마를 벌 수 있나요? - 거의 자원봉사 활동이에요.
I make very little money it's pretty much volunteer but I have some good stipends for food and I'll stay with the host family
나는 돈을 거의 벌지 않습니다. 거의 자원봉사지만 음식비도 꽤 있고 호스트 가족과 함께 지낼 거예요.
Ava is going to get a stipend a stipend is like a little bit of extra money
Ava는 봉급을 받을 예정입니다. 봉급은 약간의 추가 돈과 같습니다.
it will help cover costs if you're studying or working on a project a stipend might cover basic needs like rent food and utilities
프로젝트를 공부하거나 작업하는 경우 비용을 충당하는 데 도움이 됩니다. 봉급은 임대료, 음식, 유틸리티와 같은 기본적인 요구 사항을 충당할 수 있습니다.
that's amazing well thank you so much
정말 놀랍습니다. 정말 감사합니다!
hi what's your name Alison
안녕, 이름이 뭐예요? -앨리슨.
what do you do for a living
직업이 뭐예요?
I am currently an intern at the catalytic Fund in Northern Kentucky
저는 현재 북부 켄터키에 있는 Catalytic Fund에서 인턴으로 일하고 있습니다.
what kind of work do you do so we're a not for-profit real estate investment firm
어떤 종류의 일을 하시나요? -그래서 저희는 비영리 부동산 투자회사이기 때문에
so we basically help with like pre-development for things so that people who might not have the money to do so
돈이 없는 분들도 예쁜 건물을 지을 수 있도록 기본적으로 사전 개발 등을 도와드리고 있습니다
can build pretty buildings
.
what's your favorite part about the job I enjoy feeling like I'm making a difference
이 직업에서 가장 좋아하는 부분은 무엇인가요? -나는 변화를 만들고 있다는 느낌을 받고
and like working with like saving historical buildings
역사적인 건물을 구하는 것과 같은 일을 하는 것을 좋아합니다.
what's the least favorite part about your job my office doesn't have a window so
당신의 직업에서 가장 마음에 들지 않는 부분은 무엇입니까? - 내 사무실에는 창문이 없어서
I wish my office had a window that I could look out of
밖을 내다볼 수 있는 창문이 있었으면 좋겠다.
how many hours do you work each week between 35 and 40
매주 몇 시간 일하시나요? -35~40[시간] 사이.
how much do you earn each year currently I make 17 an hour cuz
매년 얼마를 벌나요? -현재 저는 시간당 17달러를 벌고 있습니다. 왜냐하면
it's just a summer internship while I'm in graduate school
대학원에 있는 동안 여름 인턴십을 했기 때문입니다.
okay an internship is like a temporary job where you learn about a certain field or industry
인턴십은 특정 분야나 산업에 대해 배우는 임시직과 같습니다.
think of it as a chance to try out a career before you commit to it
직업을 결정하기 전에 직업을 시험해 볼 수 있는 기회라고 생각하십시오.
hi what's your name Joe Nickel
안녕, 이름이 뭐예요? - 조 니켈.
what do you do for a living I'm an urban designer and city planner
직업이 뭐예요? -저는 도시 디자이너이자 도시 계획가입니다.
what do you like most about your job I love being able to work with people
당신의 직업에서 가장 좋아하는 점은 무엇입니까? -저는 사람들과 협력하여
to change and improve their neighborhoods their cities their towns and I like drawing
이웃, 도시, 마을을 변화시키고 개선할 수 있는 것을 좋아하며 그림 그리기를 좋아합니다.
how many hours do you work each week try to keep it under 45
매주 몇 시간 일하시나요? -45[시간] 이하로 유지하려고 노력해요.
how much do you earn every year I'm not going to answer that
매년 얼마를 벌어요? -그건 대답 안 할게요.
hi what's your name hi I'm Alex
안녕, 이름이 뭐예요? -안녕하세요, 저는 알렉스입니다.
what do you do for a living so I'm a shift supervisor at Starbucks
직업이 뭐예요? -그래서 저는 스타벅스의 교대근무 감독자입니다.
what do you do for your job so my job is running anything on the floor
당신은 직업을 위해 무엇을 합니까? -그래서 내 직업은 바닥에서 무엇이든 돌리는 것입니다.
I'm just making sure everyone's making drinks I'm just making sure everything runs smoothly
나는 단지 모두가 술을 만들고 있는지 확인하고, 모든 일이 원활하게 진행되고,
and making sure the day-to-day stuff works well
일상적인 일이 잘 진행되는지 확인하고 있습니다.
what do you like about your job I love being able to see different people
당신의 직업에서 어떤 점이 마음에 드나요? - 다양한 사람들을 만날 수 있는 걸 좋아해요.
what's the least favorite part about your job I would say dealing with the downside of
당신의 직업에서 가장 마음에 들지 않는 부분은 무엇입니까? - 많은 사람을 상대하는 것의
dealing with so many people you get like random people that think they can do whatever
단점을 해결한다고 말하고 싶습니다 . 당신은 무엇이든 할 수 있다고 생각하는 무작위 사람들처럼 보입니다.
and how many hours do you work each week so I work around 40 hours each week
매주 몇 시간 일하시나요? -그래서 일주일에 40시간 정도 일해요.
how much do you earn each week or each year each year is probably around 60 to 70,000
매주 또는 매년 얼마를 벌나요? -연간 대략 $60,000~$70,000 정도입니다.
hi what's your name my name's Kyle
안녕, 이름이 뭐예요? -제 이름은 카일이에요.
what do you do for a living I just started a new job in sales in Tampa
직업이 뭐예요? -탬파에서 영업직으로 새로 일을 시작했기
so I started in about two weeks
때문에 약 2주 후에 시작합니다.
and what kind of job do you have so I work in the elevator industry
그리고 당신은 어떤 종류의 직업을 갖고 있나요? -그래서 저는 엘리베이터 업계에 종사하고 있어서
so I'm working as a sales trade
판매업으로 일하고 있어요.
what's your favorite part about your job I just like the environment the job flexibility
당신의 직업에서 가장 좋아하는 부분은 무엇입니까? - 환경과 업무 유연성이 마음에 듭니다.
how many hours will you work each week so I typically work full time
매주 몇 시간 일할 건가요? -그래서 저는 일반적으로 풀타임으로 일하므로
so I'll be in the office 5 days a week 8 hours a day
주 5일 하루 8시간 사무실에 있습니다.
how much will you earn so I'll be around 95 my first year
당신은 얼마나 벌 것인가? -그래서 첫해에는 약 $95,000 정도가 될 것 같아요.
hopefully it's commission based so it could be above that below that
수수료 기반이므로 그 이상/이하일 수 있습니다.
a commission based job means your pay is directly tied to how much you sell or how will you perform
커미션 기반 직업은 급여가 판매 금액이나 성과에 직접적으로 연결되어 있음을 의미합니다.
the more you sell the more you earn
더 많이 판매할수록 더 많은 수익을 얻을 수 있습니다.
hi what's your name my name is Calvin Johnson
안녕, 이름이 뭐예요? -제 이름은 캘빈 존슨이에요.
what do you do for a living well I'm a retired Cincinnati Police Sergeant
직업이 뭐예요? -글쎄요, 저는 은퇴한 신시내티 경찰 경사
but now I'm a supervisor for Cincinnati Metro Transit
였지만 지금은 신시내티 메트로 교통의 감독관입니다.
Calvin retired from his job so he's not working full-time anymore
Calvin은 직장에서 은퇴하여 더 이상 풀타임으로 일하지 않습니다.
most people retire around 65 but people can retire earlier or later for different reasons
대부분의 사람들은 65세쯤에 은퇴하지만, 사람들은 다양한 이유로 더 일찍 또는 늦게 은퇴할 수 있습니다.
what do you normally do for work like what does your day-to-day look like
평소에는 어떤 일을 하시나요? 당신의 일상은 어떤 모습인가요?
supervise the coaches that drive around the city make sure they're safe getting there on time
저는 도시 주변을 운전하는 코치들을 감독하고, 그들이 제 시간에 안전하게 도착할 수 있도록 하고,
making sure we have a positive experience riding the Metro
우리가 지하철을 타고 긍정적인 경험을 할 수 있도록 합니다.
what's your favorite part about your job the people interacting with people
당신의 직업에서 가장 좋아하는 부분은 무엇입니까? - 사람들. 사람들과 교류
and being able to assist to get to A and B
하고 그들이 A와 B에 도달하도록 도울 수 있는 것.
and least favorite part about your job probably the hours right now I
그리고 당신의 직업에서 가장 마음에 들지 않는 부분은 무엇입니까? -아마 지금은
work 8 at night till 4 in the morning
밤 8시부터 새벽 4시까지 일할 것 같아요.
how many hours do you work each week in total uh 40 hours a week
귀하는 매주 총 몇 시간 일하십니까? -어, 일주일에 40시간.
how much do you earn each year probably about 80,000
매년 얼마를 벌나요? - 80만원 정도 될 것 같아요.
hi what's your name my name is Evan Hunter
안녕, 이름이 뭐예요? -제 이름은 에반 헌터예요.
what do you do for a living I'm a data scientist at Fifth Third Bank
직업이 뭐예요? -저는 Fifth Third Bank의 데이터 과학자입니다.
what's your favorite part about your job I honestly really love my co-workers
당신의 직업에서 가장 좋아하는 부분은 무엇입니까? -솔직히 동료들을 정말 사랑해요.
we have a lot of great people I work with
우리는 함께 일하는 훌륭한 사람들이 많이 있습니다.
what kind of projects do you work on I'm primarily working on our digital messaging
어떤 종류의 프로젝트를 진행하시나요? -저는 주로 디지털 메시징
chat bot Genie right now and so working a lot with our operations Partners
챗봇 지니 작업을 하고 있으며 운영 파트너와 많은 작업을 하고 있으며
working a lot with our developers who work on the chatbot figuring out what the chat bot's going to say in various circumstances
챗봇 작업을 하는 개발자들과도 많은 작업을 하고 있으며 [그리고] 다양한 상황에서 챗봇이 무엇을 말할지 알아내고 있습니다.
how many hours do you work each week 40 50 somewhere in there not too many
매주 몇 시간 일하시나요? -40-50 [시간] 어딘가에 있습니다. 너무 많지는 않습니다.
I don't work as much as many people do
나는 많은 사람들이 하는 것만큼 일을 하지 않습니다.
okay everybody I hope you guys enjoyed this video
좋아요 여러분, 이번 영상이 즐거웠기를 바랍니다.
and I hope this video gives you a glimpse of what people do for a living and how much they earn each year
그리고 이 영상을 통해 사람들이 무슨 일을 하며 매년 얼마를 벌고 있는지 엿볼 수 있기를 바랍니다.
go ahead and give me a like subscribe and I'll see you guys next week
좋아요와 구독 눌러주시고 다음주에 뵙겠습니다.
bye
안녕!